vertagear.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Vertagear

This Privacy Policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected. This Privacy Policy may change at any time. By using the Vertagear.com website, you accept the terms and conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Vertagear collects any Personal Information regarding a specific person. This information includes, but is not limited to name, address, telephone number, email address, birth date, information about the person’s activities and purchases. This also includes sensitive information, such as your credit card number.

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

At Vertagear, we collect and store your personal and transactional information in our customer database. This information is used to process your transactions, and cater to your customer service requests. You may also receive both printed and electronic communications from us about new products, discounts, and special promotions.

**AGGREGATE DATA AND INFORMATION USAGE**

Along with personal information, we collect and store records about the products purchased pages viewed by all visitors to our website. This data is aggregated to provide us with specific shopping trends on our website. Our Web servers automatically collect information about each visitor who requests Vertagear Web pages, including your computer’s IP address. Through the use of this information, we are able to tailor a unique shopping experience for our customers.

**CLICK-STREAM DATA AND COOKIE TECHNOLOGY**

Click-Stream information is used to process your order and ensure delivery to you. This information will allow us to see how what pages are visited and what features are used. In addition, this information is aggregated to disseminate current shopping trends of our consumers. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. Vertagear may also utilize cookies to analyze data as well. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. We use this information to complete, analyze and support your purchases from Vertagear.com and use of the Vertagear.com website to comply with any requirements of law and to determine the commissions for our Affiliates. This information may be provided only to our staff and any third-party involved in the completion of your transaction.

**EMAIL SUBSCRIPTION PREFERENCES**

Providing Vertagear your e-mail address opts you in to receive Vertagear e-mail newsletters. You may choose at any time to discontinue receiving e-mail newsletters by opting out or unsubscribing. Vertagear will not rent, sell or give your e-mail address to any other organization for the purposes of marketing or solicitation. Vertagear will need to supply your e-mail address to specific service providers who deliver e-mail on our behalf. However, third-party service providers are contractually prohibited from using your information for any purpose other than in accordance with the terms of their agreements with Vertagear.

*Please note: You may be contacted by email, mail, or telephone regarding any placed order on Vertagear.com

**COMMUNICATIONS FROM VERTAGEAR OTHER COMPANIES**

Vertagear may use third-party companies to help us provide products and services to you, to assist in market research, to manage personal and sensitive information, or to fulfill promotions and communicate with you.  Vertagear.com is not responsible for privacy practices of these companies. All companies that work with Vertagear are restricted from using any information in any manner other than providing you with the products and services available from Vertagear

**PRIVACY NOTES**

Vertagear may provide links to Web sites outside of Vertagear.com as an added convenience/service to the user. Additionally, affiliates of Vertagear.com may link to our site. Any link included does not imply or convey endorsement of the other company or organization, its site, or its products or services. Vertagear is not responsible for the privacy, terms of use or other policies of any other Web site.

Vertagear will release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, or protect the rights, property or safety of Vertagear.com, our users or others.

**PRIVACY POLICY CONSENT AND CHANGES**

By using the Vertagear.com web site, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page, which it is your responsibility to review frequently.
